Hi everyone! Welcome to my AWS certified Generative Air Developer
Certification course. My name is Rahul Dresil and I will guide you through
every architectural decision you need to master for this exam. Now remember
section 2 and 3 of this course are most critical for passing the exam. You can
expect multiple scenario-based questions from these topics. So please be
thorough with all the lectures that are part of these two sections. So if you
see the course outline you can see the section 2 here and then you can see the
section 3. So these two are the most important and then you can also expect some
questions from section 4. I'll be adding additional mini mock exams over next
1 to 2 weeks which will be very similar to what is being asked in the exam. Now
if you're using Udemy for the first time please note that you can adjust the
playback speed any time to match your pace. So if you believe I speak a little too
fast then you can go to this playback rate and just reduce the speed or if
you think I'm a little too slow then you can go ahead and increase the speed. Now
remember this is a new course so if you find any issue maybe a missing topic a
video that doesn't work or you see any discrepancy in the quiz question please
message me on Udemy or send me an email and I will address it in 24 to 48 hours.
And then finally if you need any further guidance on AWS certified
generative air developer exam please feel free to reach me via either LinkedIn
or send me an email at thristlerawl@gmail.com. I hope you have a great learning
experience through this course and best of luck for your exam. Thank you.